(Amy:)but it's still limited
in what it can do.
(Sheldon:)I understand.
(Sheldon:)She's the mean one,
I'm the fun one.
(Howard:)Huh, they screwed up
and gave us steamed broccoli.
(Raj:)Oh, no, that's mine.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)The last green thing
(Leonard:)I saw you eat was a Skittle.
(Raj:)Well, I can't eat
(Raj:)like a ten-year-old
all the time.
(Penny:)You're dating somebody,
who is it?
(Raj:)What?
(Raj:)What are you talking about?
(Penny:)You only watch what you
eat when you're afraid
(Penny:)you might have
to take your shirt off.
(Howard:)No, she's right.
(Howard:)As long as I've known you,
(Howard:)you've always been
self-conscious
(Howard:)about your cleavage.
It's because you keep trying
(Raj:)to stick pencils in it.
(Penny:)All right, fine,
don't tell us.
(Raj:)There's nothing to tell.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Leonard:)How's that broccoli?
(Raj:)It's gross but I have to eat it
because I met somebody.
(Penny:)Bam.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Penny:)What's her name?
Issabella.
(Howard:)Oh, did you meet
her at work?
(Raj:)Yes, in the telescope room.